Downloaded @ subs4free.club
Sorry about
the delays today, folks,
but ground control is telling me
it's gonna be another 15 or so
until we can start
the deplaning process.
So just sit tight
and we'll have you on your
way as soon as we can.
Seatbelts.
Ma'am. Ma'am. Seatbelt.
Excuse me...
Please stay seated
until we're at the gate.
Ow! What the fuck?
Sorry. No, I had to grab...
- You fell asleep on me.
- Why would I do that?
When did we land?
Me again, folks.
I'm now being told that
the stairway they've got
on the tarmac here doesn't
actually fit our aircraft.
So we'll get you on the ground
as soon as we figure
out what that means.
Oh...
♪ Beetles and eggs and blues ♪
♪ And pour a little
everything else ♪
♪ You steam a lens
stable Eyes and glass ♪
♪ Not get pissed off through ♪
♪ My bird lips as good news ♪
♪ Still we can ♪
I think I'm frozen here
because it's been
saying six minutes.
I know we're close but...
Hello?
Can you hear me? Did
I lose you? Hello?
Hello?
Oh, no. Navigation
crashed too.
God, what the...
Hey, does your phone...
I don't have any
reception. I can't...
Well, if you don't have
service, why would I?
Oh, uh, wait.
You know what? I...
I have emailed directions.
Can you put your window up?
The pollen is killing me.
Thank you.
So, hey, look, I just wanna say,
you know, thanks again for...
you know, being here.
Stop picking.
Hey, stop picking.
Come on. Don't.
Did you just try to flick me?
Come on. There's no
reason to be nervous.
You're here to enjoy yourself.
That's definitely not...
why I'm here.
Yeah. But you
still can, right?
Huh? Take in some nature,
maybe join me on a trail run?
Or not.
But it's your loss.
The mountains this far north,
pristine. Truly.
Untouched by man.
Look, I get
you don't wanna be here
but Odell, the Leopolds,
they have a big
thing about family
and they just assume
that you and I
are particularly close
because of everything
that, you know,
'cause of everything
that's happened to us.
Because of everything
that's happened to us?
Yeah.
Or are you just talking
about the one thing?
Look, I'm sorry. I just don't
feel like being a pity prop
- for the single dad thing...
- Oh, come on. That's...
...that you've got going on
with your bosses. That's all.
No. That's not
what this is about.
No. We can... We
can own it though.
I mean, we could really milk
them for their sympathy.
I could fake a limp.
Maybe I could prepare a, a
weepy monologue about Mom.
But I don't know, you probably
would have to give notes on it
and we need some
more time for that.
Okay. That's it.
Whatever this is,
just get it out of your
system before we get there.
Are you talking
about my personality?
Fine. I will sit
there and smile
while they plan
their predatory price
gouging at the dinner table.
Their day-to-day is so
far above drug pricing.
And they care about
a lot of things,
not just pharmaceuticals.
I mean, this entire nature
preserve was donated by them.
Yeah, but you know that
philanthropy is just...
It's reputation laundering
for the oligarchy.
Yeah. Okay. All right.
Maybe on the arts quad,
but in the real world,
you have to compromise.
Once I'm named proxy
and I sit on this board
for five, six years,
ten tops,
then I will earn enough to
make sure that we're okay
no matter what hits us, alright?
Right.
- Uh. Odell.
- It's Griffin.
Mr. Leopold was expecting
you over an hour ago.
What? Didn't
you get my texts?
- No.
- Oh God, roaming.
Um, no,
let him know that we will
literally be there any minute.
Elliot, where are you?
Oh, yes. Yeah, I'm so sorry
about this, Mr. Leopold.
- We... It's been a whole...
- You need to slow down.
No. I need service. Hello?
Elliot, how long
is this drive going to take?
Hello? Can you
hear me? Can you hear me?
He
sounds like a robot
- getting waterboarded?
- Hello?
Here. Call him back.
Do it yourself. This
is all for you anyway.
What? What are you talking...
Oh, my God! Use a tissue.
That's disgusting.
Are you okay? Are you okay?
You couldn't watch
the fucking road?
Uh... It's okay. It's
okay. We're okay.
I got the damage
waiver. It's...
What the fuck was that?
I don't think it's dead.
Just wait there.
What?
What, uh, I mean, uh...
It's suffering.
You, you think it's
endangered or...
Um, we, we can't, we can't
just leave it here, right?
I mean...
Fuck!
If a ranger finds it then...
I mean, no one uses this road.
God, I'm late and
I'm going to prison.
Ridley, are you okay?
Let go!
Ridley!
Stop! Stop!
Sorry we're late.
Welcome to the lodge.
Lodge? Wow.
Counselor! What happened?
You walk from the
airport or what?
You,
you would not believe.
Forget it. That's a joke.
I got it from here, Shaw.
Such a card, Shepard.
I'm so sorry we're late.
How are you? Your folks here?
Don't know where else they'd be.
I was about to hit the tub,
but come in here for a
cut of the good stuff.
Oh, thank you.
Uh, this is my daughter, Ridley.
Shep Leopold.
- Good to know you.
- Is that Elliot?
Perfect timing.
I just got off a Zoom
with the Foundation
about the refugees,
we're evacuating them.
Or are we vaccinating them?
It's so good to...
Now, I need to
apologize in advance.
Odell is very
sensitive about word
of his condition getting out,
hence the skeleton
staff around here.
Oh, yeah. We're all making
sacrifices.
Ah, here he is.
And we'd
almost assumed the worst.
I'm so sorry to
keep you waiting, Odell.
These things happen.
How was the drive
through the pass?
Get lucky, spot any
big game on the way in?
Uh, unfortunately, no.
But it, it was just lovely.
Uh, the mountains,
right? The air...
You okay, my dear?
What?
Yeah. Sorry.
Just, um, just not feeling good.
Oh, no.
Do you need to lie down?
Griff can show you to your room.
- No. I, uh...
- Are you sure?
He loves doing it.
Might not be a bad idea.
I just don't feel
like we can stay...
Sorry?
...for
the whole weekend.
Well, you must stay
for dinner, darling.
Griff is making my
famous moussaka.
Mmm.
I don't know, Mom. She
doesn't look so hot.
You have something on your face,
just so you know.
Maybe you should
splash some water on yourself,
see if that helps.
I was like her at that age.
Hormones.
Uh-hmm.
- Griff?
- Griff!
- Odell wants to move.
Having exhausted
traditional treatment options,
I made peace with my mortality.
And so, in preparing
for the bardo,
I meditated on who might
best liaise between my family
and my family
business in my absence
and you soon came
to mind, Elliot.
I knew that Belinda and Shep
would agree with me once
they got to know you.
Well, I'm so happy to
hear you say that, Odell,
because I see this
as the start of a long-term
family relationship.
Power of attorney and proxy
agreements cover all...
Um...
Sorry. Sorry.
Power of attorney
and proxy agreements
uh, cover all points
previously discussed,
with me representing the
family's board interests
at Leopold Laboratories.
So Belinda can focus
on the foundation.
And, Shepard, you're free
to pursue your, uh...
My diversified portfolio of
entrepreneurial activities.
Yeah, we all know.
Hard sciences never could
much contain my interests.
That's right, Sheppie.
Exactly. So, no
surprises here.
- And...
- Sit down.
Oh. Um...
Well, um, once I'm situated
in my new position,
there are some opportunities
both in and outside
of the pharma space
that I'd love to get into, but,
for now, just, signatures...
I appreciate your lack
of foreplay but...
That he certainly does.
...the whole point here
was to go slow, wasn't it?
I...
We want to know you as a person,
not the VP of
Ethics & Compliance
that wins the company
fun run every year.
Oh. Well,
it's only a 10K.
And to truly know someone,
you need to know their family.
Which is
why we insisted
young Ridley join
us for the weekend.
Yes. And, and
here we are and yet
we have no idea what she's
studying at university.
Art history.
Or I don't...
Actually, I don't know.
Uh, undecided, um, maybe.
Dad?
Sorry.
I need you in there and
I need you to be normal.
They won't sign until
they get to know you.
No. We have to go deal
with our baggage. Now.
Something is going on
- with that thing.
- Okay.
I think it's calling out
to me. I can feel it.
Okay. Look, it's
dead. It's dead.
I need you to keep it together
and act like everything is fine.
And then I will bury it tonight
when everyone else is asleep
and they'll never
know what happened
and we never have
to talk about it
ever again.
Oh, my.
I'm so sorry.
Uh, it seems as if Ridley
is, uh, quite sick.
Like some kind of bug. It
might be contagious even.
So I'm thinking I should
just drive her back
to the airport. Now.
What's wrong? What's
going on here?
Is this some sort of
negotiating tactic?
No, it's not. Um,
I... I... I promise.
In fact, look, I
can drop her off.
I can come right back and
even answer any quest...
Wait.
You're gonna what?
- Hmm?
- Elliot,
when I told them about you,
I told them about
your character.
Right. My character.
About your mettle in
the face of hardship,
how you and your daughter
have made a go of it
these past years after
your wife passed on.
- Right. Well...
- Your loyalty,
and dedication to the
company in that time.
Because that's the commitment
that'll be required.
- This is fucked.
- Even if that means...
- ...serving as a buffer.
This is so fucked.
Are you... Are
you okay, m'lady?
Uh, no, I'm, I'm fine.
I, just, there's...
No, you don't have to...
Mr. Leopold, sir.
Yes? Uh, what is it?
You know, I'm not sure.
- Uh...
- Have a look.
Is that...
Is there something in your car?
What did you say?
What? No.
By the look
of their bonnet,
my guess is they
struck an animal.
- Belinda.
- Is that it?
You strike something
with your car then?
- No.
- Strike something with...
No. Did you?
Well, what's
in your car then?
Luggage.
Did you not even kill it, guy?
What are you on
about? What is this?
Oh!
Okay. Now, granted, this
is gonna sound odd but...
Wait, wait, wait!
I don't think I should be in-in,
in swim shorts for this moment.
I know a lot of species
in this area are rare.
Um, but, uh, is this exact,
uh, you know, familiar to you?
Familiar to us? No.
This is new.
This doesn't seem novel to you?
Um, yes, it is novel, uh,
now that you mention it.
What exactly are we
saying this is though?
I think we know
exactly what it is.
What I can say with-with
total confidence
is Elliot here has hit a,
a horse-like, uh, Mammalia,
uh, vertebralia, would
that be the correct...
- Yes, yes.
- ...um, classification?
No. But it is horse-shaped
with some sort of
protrusion or growth.
Right. That's
my working theory, too.
Feral horse, mad, tumor-ridden.
Uh, jumps in the
middle of the road,
not the fault of any
one driver, per se.
It's a fucking unicorn.
It does seem like a unicorn.
Oh, coming, sir.
What have you done?
Uh, we hit it with the car.
And then I blunt
force traumatized it,
out of sympathy.
And its blood got
all over my face.
Yeah. That's right.
Your...
Your, your face.
What is it?
It's a face. What?
It's my acne.
But, darling, you
don't have any acne.
Not anymore.
And how are you feeling?
All tip-top? And no adverse
side effects to speak of?
No.
And you've had no
other contact with it?
Well, some... Some
of it got in my eyes.
I admit I maybe went
a little overboard
with the tire iron, but...
My allergies.
Oh.
Should I call someone?
Yes! Yes, um, that we
could call the Sierra Club,
uh, but there's also the
World Wildlife Foundation...
I'm sorry, my child,
but this will have to go
governmental, I'm afraid.
And that means
military, doesn't it?
Uh, no, I don't... I
don't think we have to...
Or perhaps you're right.
Perhaps, we might ideate
outside of the box
for an alternative.
Yes. I mean, there must be
something that we can do.
I mean, as someone
who works with NGOs,
believe me, you do not
want a bunch of bureaucrats
mucking around in a
delicate situation.
- Do you?
- Mm-hmm. Right.
In my opinion,
we have a debt owed to
the spirit of this animal
to navigate by our
own moral compasses
and allow its mysteries
to reveal themselves
so that we can
honor it in a manner
that the public sector
simply cannot.
Yes. Then we will be
able to shield Elliot
from the consequences
of what seemed
a perfectly innocent
accident, right?
- Yes.
That's the spirit.
Summon Dr. Song and his
mobile laboratory posthaste.
And the security contractors.
We'll need an
escort.
Hey, can I come in?
You're already in.
Right.
Hey. You missed
some good moussaka.
You want me to see if there
are any leftovers or...
Griff brought me
a sandwich, so...
Oh, great. Well,
you love sandwiches.
Sandwiches are the best.
I'm sorry, did you
want something?
No, no, no. No, I was just,
you know, I wanted to check in.
See how...
Look, I know we
haven't talked a lot
since you left for school,
but are you okay?
I don't really
know what happened
when you touched that thing.
But thankfully, I stepped
in to save the day.
You thought I needed protecting?
Yeah. You, you didn't
see what happened.
You had like a
seizure or something.
No. No.
It wasn't...
I mean, yes, something happened,
but I wouldn't... It
wasn't anything bad.
It kinda felt like it
was showing me something.
- Forget it.
- What?
No, 'cause you're looking at
me like I'm fucking crazy.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Look, I want... I want to hear,
but you're not... giving much.
Okay. Well, I tried
to tell you earlier
when it was still in the
trunk, but you didn't listen.
I was kind of in the
middle of something
- if you hadn't noticed.
- That thing and I,
we're, like, connected.
And ever since it
died, I just...
I get this feeling I don't think
we're supposed to be here.
Like it was a mistake
handing that creature over
to these people.
Right. Okay. Right. I see.
All right, look, you
had a weird experience,
and I will pay for
the extra therapy,
but I don't see what we stand
to gain by making this weekend
all about you and your
special connection
to a magical dead horse.
Ridley?
Riddles?
Skin does look great, Rid.
Look, uh...
Sweetheart, I...
I just need you to trust me.
And that I know how to
play this situation.
Unicorn-wise.
I'm looking out for us.
Okay.
I love you.
Is that you, Elliot?
I like how you handled
things today.
Good job.
Ahh. Danke.
I can see why you've
done so well at the firm.
Ah.
Though I gotta say,
never would've guessed
what kinda meat you
were packing, buddy.
Oh. Well, it's,
it's all our meat
now, I suppose.
That it is.
Tell you what.
Why don't you hop in?
We can chop it up,
talk about your future.
Oh, no, no. I, I didn't, um...
I didn't actually pack
a, a bathing suit so...
Stickler. I get
it. That's okay.
Griff!
Get Elliot a suit!
Oh, oh, no, no, really.
It's, it's okay.
- Are you sure?
- Yeah, yeah.
- He doesn't mind. Okay.
- No, no. I'm...
Griff! Forget it!
So tell me, I was wondering.
What's her deal by the way?
She doesn't really
like you, huh?
What? No. Why
would you say that?
I don't know 'cause
it seems like it.
I mean, no offense meant, El.
Why don't you get in?
We can hot tub about it.
Think it must be moose
mating season or something.
I was about done anyhow.
Pass me that robe.
See ya.
The
crown jewel of The Met's
Medieval Collection
of the Cloisters.
The Unicorn Tapestries
are among the most
beautiful and complex works
to have survived
from the Middle Ages.
The seven tapestries
illustrate a cautionary
tale of a Lord
and his hunters pursuit
of a mystical unicorn,
which defends itself
and proves untameable.
That is until it is entranced
by a purehearted maiden.
The unicorn is pacified
by the maiden's virtue.
The creature is then killed
and brought to a castle
where it is resurrected
and kept in captivity.
However, the tapestry depicting
the unicorn and the
maiden is incomplete,
having been damaged during
the French Revolution.
But this reconstructed
restoration
tells of a vengeful
and violent beast.
It's mercilessness
and ferocity matched
only by how much it
was coveted by man.
Ridley
Kintner, come with us.
Whoa. Wait. What are you
doing? What the fuck?
Take a seat.
Okay.
Just follow my finger.
Subject one displays
negligible irritation
of epidermis.
Same,
with two's irises.
Yooo, what the hell, man?
Trying to do my job here.
Though comprehensive
analysis won't be possible
until the specimen
is transported
to Leo Labs Campus,
even with our limited
genomic testing
capabilities in the field,
we can say that
this is not a horse.
We've begun analysis of the
blood sample's reactivity
with subject one's facial dermis
and subject two's
sinus cavities,
vitreous body,
and ocular lenses.
Preliminary analysis
has revealed
some very interesting results...
Are you doing...
is there, like, an omelet
station or is that not a...
...decreased vitreous
liquid and increased...
We need to talk.
After you left last night,
I started doing
research on unicorns
and I think we
need to be careful.
Those tapestries at the
museum that Mom took us to.
- Do you remember that?
- What...
What... No... Uh, I don't know.
But, uhm, can we talk later?
This science stuff's important.
But early indicators, uh,
indicate that the blood's
therapeutic characteristics
may very well relate
to the horn itself.
- Oh, yeah?
- How?
To say would
be conjecture.
- Conject.
- Conjecture is good.
We can work with conjecture.
I don't think anyone
minds conjecting.
- Well the, um...
- Seems to be
some sort of organ.
Uh, uh...
See, somehow it's still
firing bioelectrical signals
to depolarize cells throughout
the entire nervous system,
which is weird.
Yes, bioelectromagnetic
conductivity
does seem unusual,
uh, potentially significant
in compound 1-Delta.
Excuse me. Hi.
Elliot Kintner, J.D.,
uh, subject one... or
well, two, actually.
Regardless, uh,
made the discovery,
it's good to be
working with you.
What's
that compound now?
Pulverized horn.
- We need to study it.
- Oh.
But it's potentially
more potent than the blood.
Well, what
are we waiting for?
I say we pop that
sucker off right away,
grind it up and get it crackin'.
Or is that... Is that maybe,
maybe not what the move is...
For centuries,
the Cavitenos of the Philippines
have carried on a tradition
of burying their
dead inside trees.
When the elder is ready,
they venture into nature
to select it themselves.
If this doesn't work,
that may be the last earthly
business for me to do.
No stone
unturned, darling.
Wait, if what doesn't work?
Omelet, sir?
Thank you.
Sir,
electromagnetic radiation
is still emanating
from the horn.
But it's...
...stronger.
How are
you feeling, sir?
Oh, I believe it's
working. I do believe.
Of course it is,
Odell. Of course.
Oh, yeah. No, I
bet. It's working.
Working those tumors real good.
I want to thank you
for this gift, Elliot.
The gift of
certainty. To pass on,
to be buried, or in my case,
cryogenically frozen in
a subterranean bunker,
but, regardless, to do so
knowing you've tried it
all.
Thanks to you, I have.
I do wish I'd gone to space,
though.
Yeah. Well, not
many people have.
Whatever comes of this,
you'll receive your royalty.
Understand?
Your discovery, your cut.
Perhaps, you'll become a
partner in all of this.
Thank you, sir.
I'd be grateful.
I know you would, amigo.
Did I tell you we're
on Blackfoot land?
Their people express
their thanks, grati...
Save your strength, Odell.
No one needs to hear about that.
Not now, not ever, darling.
Just... That's it. Shhh.
He's fine.
Come on.
What's going on in here?
Uh, I'm researching,
I guess.
Hmm.
What kind of researching?
Feedback's a good thing.
Don't be afraid of it.
Right. Um, I don't know.
I... I guess I just
kind of figured,
you know, what if
people used to think
that unicorns were real
because they actually were?
You know, like, we're the
ones who got it wrong.
And I feel like if
that's the case, then...
- Hmm.
- ...what people used to
have to say about them is
actually a lot more relevant
than what we think now.
Yeah, but this, this
is all just bad faith
archaic misogynist bullshit.
But some of this's actually...
- Totally.
- I'll show you.
Tell you what, why don't we
get you situated properly.
- Griff?
- Yes?
Uh, my large format printer.
I was a real shutterbug
for a few months a
couple years back
before I got into
archery and that kinda...
- Um...
- ...took over everything.
But, um...
why don't you organize
your thoughts, you know,
print some of this stuff off,
and then we can present
our research to my parents.
- What do you think?
- Yeah. Uh,
I don't know. Yeah, I
guess, I could, uh...
It doesn't have to be like a
proper mood board or anything,
but I'm a visual thinker so...
Right.
Hmm. I can't
wait to see it. Ridley.
Oh, and, uh, matte paper,
yeah? Glossy's gauche.
Dad?
Hmm.
Odell. You look...
rested.
If these protein and
tumor markers are accurate,
your cancer seems to
be in some sort of, uh,
spontaneous remission.
What's that now?
We can't say anything definitive
and right now N only equals one.
But there's a chance
this is possibly, uh...
It could be the, uh...
Cure for cancer?
Are you kidding me?
Cancer? That... That's
the biggest one.
It's a top three disease, easy.
Are you sure about that?
I mean, you've checked
your math and chemistry
and everything?
I mean, I just don't wanna
get our hopes up, darling.
I no longer need
hope now. I feel it.
It's gone, out of
my body for good.
We've done it. We
found my cure, Bella.
Oh.
Well, we can't say
anything right now,
other than it's promising.
But we might be
curing cancer here?
You hear that,
Rid? Doing good.
I can feel every cell
- in my body buzzing...
- What?
- ...vibrating...
- What's wrong?
...on the universe's
frequency.
I've never been so alive.
Oh, my God. They're
gonna hate us
on the non-profit circuit.
Nice knowing ya, cancer
charities, am I right?
Let's just slow
down for a second.
No, dear. Now's the
time to go fast.
We need to get that
creature into HQ
to replicate that
compound post-haste.
- Well... But we can't.
- Excuse me?
We can't reproduce this.
Oh, you gotta say
something else, Song.
- He's not gonna like that.
- These protein sequences
shouldn't exist, not
even theoretically.
They'd be impossible
to synthesize.
Whatever the cost, I don't care.
Do not touch those samples!
I wasn't. I was
just looking at it.
If you gave
us all the time
and all the resources
in the world,
we couldn't reproduce this.
Sometimes, science can only be
humbled in the face of nature.
For years, you've sworn
that there's no treatment
for what ails me,
and yet when I find
the cure myself,
you say you can't replicate it?
An opportunity for greatness,
for immortality, handed to you,
and all you can speak
of is man's limitations?
Man has no limitations.
So if you can't recognize
the alchemical miracle on hand,
the potential for
your legacy and mine,
then we may need a new head
of pharmaceutical
fucking research!
I understand you're
disappointed.
But you are still cured, so...
Net positive, I'd say.
So, this is it?
All we have?
It's like an NFT.
I've told you about that before.
Oh, I understand.
Supply is scarce.
Demand will be
high. I understand.
You got the Davos
guest list handy?
Always. Let's
prioritize anyone
who's had a public health scare.
The worse, the better.
And I'll
mix up some drinks.
Finally get to show
you that mixology, Pop.
Um, sorry. Can I help with
whatever is happening?
Roll up your
shirtsleeves, partner.
It's new, Priscilla.
It's not the
sort of thing we...
Excuse me. I...
...would let the FDA get
their grubby little hands on.
Just think of it
as an investment
- in your and Mark's health.
- Well, how do I sound?
Oh, great, 'cause I feel great.
How's the colon?
- No, no, no, no.
- Excuse me.
Let me tell you about
this new treatment.
Sir, can
I just have a...
Yeah. No, it's extraordinary.
I just think MBS
would think this is
a cool opportunity if
you brought it to him.
...Unlike
anything on the market.
Right, because
we've partied before
and I know what he's like.
- Dad. Dad.
- Wait, hold on...
Hold on just a second, Rid.
Three grams at two and a half.
Right. Okay. Two
and a half at 300.
No, no, three at 2.5.
- Oh, sorry. Sorry. Yeah.
- Sharp ears. Do better.
Uh, you're right. I apologize.
- What's going on?
- Oh, my gosh.
I've never seen so much
money before in my life.
I think this is gonna
change things for us.
All right.
Finish your prep!
- Holy shit.
- Let's bag the beast to go
We're going wheels
up ricky-tick.
So, my boy says the Crown Prince
and his cousin are gonna
want an eight ball to start.
What?
I mean, uh, three
and a half grams.
That's such an oddly
specific number.
Yeah. I don't know. Weird,
but that's what he said.
Wait, is this...
What? Every part
of the buffalo.
Wish I had my bitters from home,
but it's an imperfect
world. Kanpai.
The price is the price.
No, I won't be pushed around
like some labor leader.
Good. My office will call.
You're right. This is
absolutely delicious.
I haven't had this much fun
since we launched
Fen-Phen in '94.
And I thought Etherium
was a good investment.
Which it was, to be clear.
Uh, how are those
numbers looking, El?
Uh, I don't know.
I think we made, uh, a lot?
And still plenty of surplus
for the family reserves.
Fuck yes. We're
gonna live forever.
But we can't take it.
See, 'cause, look, I've
been doing some research.
Well, isn't
she enterprising?
So, the
thing is
unicorns used to be seen
differently, all right?
Hundreds and thousands
of years ago,
they were seen as, like,
these divine monsters,
but they were
impossible to catch,
except everyone totally
tried because, you know,
since forever,
people fully believed
that they could heal
literally anything.
Uh, yeah, welcome to,
like, 10 minutes ago.
Yeah, I know,
which made me wanna
check this research again
because it's right.
And Dad, do you remember
when Mom took us
to see these tapestries?
No, no, I... I don't remember.
Yes, yes, yes, you do!
- What?
- The Cloisters, remember?
- I don't. I'm sorry. I...
- She said it was
her favorite museum
when she was little.
She took us like a month
after her diagnosis and it...
What does that have
to do with anything?
Yeah. I'm sorry. Where
are we going with this?
I have to admit,
I'm a bit lost in the woods
on this one too, darling.
Just...
you just have to look at
these tapestries, okay?
They're from the Middle Ages,
they're literally famous
and they tell this whole story,
one that reoccurs over and over.
And, you know,
people always thought
that they were a
metaphor for Christ
and man's inherent corruption,
which actually makes sense
in historical context
considering the church
was commissioning
art-making as a way
to enforce obedience.
But that doesn't
matter. What matters is,
I don't think that we're
supposed to have this, okay?
Because if unicorns are real,
which we know that they are,
then these stories might be too.
And you expect
us to alter course
and invest in a
theory based on this?
Yeah. This
has no flow, okay?
I told you to make a mood
board, not a... shit board.
I, I don't get it.
What would you have us do,
leave it outside to rot?
- Yes.
- No.
- No one is suggesting that.
- I am.
It's coming with us, sweetheart.
And it's gonna help
a lot of people.
Well, not a lot of people.
But good people. Our people.
I am telling you
right now, we can't.
Bad things will
happen. I can feel it.
Doesn't that count for anything?
No?
The arrogance, to claim
to know such things
that are unknowable.
Does she represent
your family's interests
in this venture?
I don't know what she's
talking about, Odell.
I don't. I mean,
she doesn't know
what she's talking
about. Right?
I know that you are standing up
for your principles
and I am proud of you for it,
but we don't need to perform
for each other here
and now, do we?
We've got
time for bubbles before
we hit the airport, right?
Here's to being reborn.
Change in plans.
And here's hoping we kill
Bigfoot on the way home, eh?
Oh, Sheppie.
Careful, Dr. Song.
That's your responsibility
in transport.
Asset is on the move.
Asset is on the...
Bloody comms.
Is the convoy
prepped? Can anyone read me?
Why don't you go
and have a look see?
Oh, rea...
Oh, okay. Right.
Hello?
Hey.
What happened?
Ugh. Ew.
- Bring it to us!
- Come on! Let's go!
Sheppie, come!
Dawdle-fucking-not!
Open fire!
I'll just
get out of your way.
Cease fire!
Ridley, go to the
car! I'm coming!
Surround
her! Take it down!
Fall back!
Help me! Help me!
Don't move.
Stay right there.
On three,
run inside, okay?
We're not doing this right now.
- Alright. One...
- No.
- ...two...
- Stop counting.
...three,
go!
Hey!
Are you okay?
Are you all right? Are
you... Are you hurt?
No, I'm
fine, I'm fine.
Got you.
The possibilities are
absolutely extraordinary.
Listen, it's-you sure
it didn't bite you?
No, I, I already
said that I'm fine.
- If it has rabies...
- I already said that I'm fine.
Or if you need shots,
it might not...
Okay. But I told you something
like this would happen
- and you chose not to listen.
- I know. But, no, no, no, no.
- I already told you.
- You didn't tell me anything.
Maybe if you'd had a
more specific warning,
we could have left already.
How did you know it
would be this way?
From your folkloric curricula?
- No, no. No, no, no.
- I'm saying something.
Okay, 'cause it's not
just the research.
Because yesterday,
I touched its horn.
I kind of had like a
vision or something.
I don't really know
how to explain it,
but it, it felt like it
was showing me something.
Go on, little
sister. Regale me.
All I can say is,
after that happened,
I feel connected to that thing,
like I have some sort of bond.
And the same thing
with the bigger one.
And so you think that's
why it didn't hurt you?
Yeah. I don't
know. I think, maybe.
I think it wants us to
just leave its baby and go.
It did attack when Dr. Song
was moving the young one,
so, yeah, she might have a...
I hear you. In fact,
you've convinced me
that the only way to be
as good of an advocate
for these creatures as you are
is to recover this wounded
adult before it expires
so that I can understand
this experience of
yours first-hand.
See, now we're talking sense.
You see how that
feels different?
No, that's like the opposite
of what I just said.
- Hey.
- No bad ideas, Rid.
Not to be a
size queen, as they say,
but that horn was
rather girthsome.
Yes. And it was used
to kill your guards!
And Dr. Dennis Young-Jo Song.
And wouldn't it be cruel
to let them die in vain?
Think of that animal out
there bleeding to death,
suffering, alone
in the wilderness.
I feel very strongly
that we can't just go out
and, and, and strip
mine another one.
Come on.
They have cured everything
that we've thrown at them.
So I'd say we have
a moral imperative
to harvest every last
one. Got it, horse girl?
Hey, easy.
He is crass,
but he's right.
We do this not for
our own benefit,
but for the betterment
of the world.
Hmm. Brava.
Medium rare as you
requested, sir.
All right.
Okay. You know what?
Just spitballing here, what
if Ridley and I go home,
we take the, the
little one with us,
you know, for safekeeping
just in case...
So you'd retreat in the
face of opportunity?
And here I thought you
were invested, Elliot.
Sweat equity.
Oh, no, no. No,
that's not what I...
I say, any man who
abandons his partner
is no partner of mine.
If you can't see this through,
then it's certainly
for the best.
That your services
are no longer required
as my family's proxy.
You know what? Forget it.
It turns out there, there
are bad ideas after all.
Let's, uh, let's do your thing.
What, what is your thing?
Pack your scran
and call your nan!
Hunting party moves out in five!
Um, has anyone
seen the bug spray?
So, uh, before Dr. Song...
uh-before what happened,
the electromagnetic
detector went off
and Denny saw it. And he
looked at me and, You know...
I think this has
DEET in it if you...
Did you know the Maasai warriors
hunt lions with only a spear?
Remarkable rite of passage.
Reminds you of man's innate
capacity, don't you think?
Hmm.
Me personally, I've only done it
with an automatic assault rifle.
Not unlike this model.
Oh, so you've,
like, killed lions?
Oh, I certainly have, partner.
Lions, elephants, great apes.
Right. Wow.
Hey, you know, regarding
the whole partner thing,
it might be great to
formalize some of that,
you know, just in case.
When we're back, amigo.
I'll get you fresh beads, sir.
- Do.
- Disappointing news
but it seems like ole Griff
can't find my
compound bow, so...
- Dad...
- I thought now would be like
a perfect time for me
to just hit the tub
- and start...
- Do us a favor,
- save the excuses.
- It's not an excuse.
Someone needs to stay
here and brainstorm
how to brand away from the
whole "unicorn murder" thing
and you know that's where
I do my best thinking.
I don't care if that
thing is dead out there,
you can't go with them.
We can't be a part
of this anymore.
I have to keep our stake,
you know, staked down.
You were right, they're
not great people, but...
...uh, I will tag
along with them,
I'll watch them
haul this corpse in,
and then you and I, you
know, we'll finally be set.
If you go out
there, I'm leaving.
This is a good thing.
What if Mom was able to
get something like this?
They wouldn't even
let her get near it.
Can you please, please
just listen and not go?
Can you please stay with me?
Elliot, it's time to
collect our spoils.
- I won't be long, all right?
- Dad, no.
You'll thank me
for this someday.
Misguided, but at
least she's got
some intellectual
rigor about her.
Tough loss.
Cuts deep, I bet.
Yeah.
But doesn't it feel
like it's kind of
how he might've wanted
to go, you know?
Not really, no.
But isn't it?
You know, in pursuit of science.
And so he's gone.
What do we do now?
Do we sulk?
Lament?
Be weak?
I don't think that's
what I'm doing.
Or do we keep pushing? Huh?
Keep pushing the science
and maintain his
intellectual rigor...
- Can you put that down?
- ...honor his life's work?
Or maybe he's not
worth remembering?
Of course, he is.
Exactly.
And that's why I think
you need to get back in there,
get back to work, make him proud
and saw the horn off
that fucking pony,
what do you say?
The h-I thought we
were talking like
a commemorative
plaque or something.
Oh, no, no. No, there's
no time for that.
Horn first, then
plaque. All right?
Sorry.
Just a
little... little bit.
For science.
Ugh.
All right.
The unicorn is killed.
Then it's resurrected.
Then it's resurrected?
Oh, shit.
Shit, shit, shit.
Do us a favor.
Save the excuses, Bhatia.
It's not
an excuse, okay?
We tried.
But the horn, the
organ, whatever it is,
it seems to be signaling for...
I mean, cellular swelling,
mitochondrial dysfunction,
all typical signs
of postmortem decay
and decomposition.
They're not just slowing,
they're reversing.
Hold the phone, Ponce de Leon.
You're saying it
won't stay dead?
Maybe. Yeah, maybe.
- Maybe, yeah. yeah.
- Yeah?
I want that horn in my hand.
- Hey.
- Oh, shit.
- Shit. Sorry.
- Oh, my God.
Sorry. Podcast.
Do you have a way to get in
contact with them somehow?
Because I think
that these things
might be able to,
like, heal themselves
and that means my
dad, Odell, Shaw...
- Yes, right.
- ...they all... They just need
to get back here now.
Okay. Um...
It...
Nothing
from Odell, right?
Sorry.
Fuck!
- Hey, we gotta go right now.
- Calm down.
What do
the arrows mean?
Contact!
Shoot it!
Tighten up.
Alert.
Oh, thank you.
Uh...
Odell?
Here.
Did you kill them?
Did I kill them?
Fucking unskilled labor.
Oh!
Okay then.
Just us.
Aren't you the most
magnificent thing?
You like me, don't you?
I'm harmless.
That's it, amigo.
Just a little touch.
Now you can show
me your secrets.
Come on.
That's right.
Now give me the horn.
If you'll just excuse me.
Pardon me, thank you.
He's gone. He's
really finally gone.
There are two of them?
No, no,
no, put that back.
My dad died for that thing.
Hey, you cannot go outside. I
almost got killed out there.
This is how we stop people
from getting killed.
We need to give their baby back.
Everyone needs to calm down!
We need to take
control of the situation.
Yeah. Yeah, you're right.
What would Odell do?
Probably hire
me to look after you
- and I'd call the police.
- Relax. My dad only
brought you on to be the last
line of plausible deniability.
This really isn't
the best use of time.
- It's okay.
- Fine, do it.
Make the call. Just
give me a minute.
Well,
you know so much.
Do they ever catch these things
in your draperies or
needlepoint of stories?
No, I mean, yeah,
but the lore becomes
more metaphorical or...
Wait, they're
doing something
by the electrical equipment.
RCMP. Bonjour.
- Hello, hello, officer?
- How can I help you?
Oh, thank God.
Hello. Hello. Hello?
Wait, what happened?
What happened?
The cellular booster
uses, um, house power.
The fuck was that? I'm
trying to grieve in there!
Do you think that there was
enough time to trace the call?
- How does tracing work?
- Forget that.
We're taking this out and
giving its child back.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
The gate... The
gate is electric.
There's no point in
us giving it back
if we're just gonna
be trapped out there
with those things
that killed Odell.
God damn it, Odie!
Someone has to access
the gate's motor housing
in order to manually
open it, ma'am.
So, unfortunately,
until we do that,
no one is driving out of here.
Then we draw straws.
You're not drawing anything.
It's only fair.
Well, protective
parenting aside,
I mean is chance
really the best way
to decide anything?
Generally not very
scientific, no.
Exactly. No, no.
First, we must ask ourselves,
who is most familiar
with the gate?
That's right, that's
right because, uh,
that would be the person
who has the greatest chance
of, uh, succeeding, right?
- Yes.
- Hang on a minute.
You can't just volunteer
me to go out there.
Years of service and
we have never asked
anything of you except this.
Well, that's not true,
and even if it were...
Or we could vote on it.
- I vote for Griff.
- Seconded.
- I vote for not Griff.
- Thank you. As do I.
Yes. But sweetie,
you're not even 21 yet.
- So?
- You know,
it's not particularly
complicated.
It's not like I'm
the fucking gate guy!
Although, in this instance,
it kind of seems like
you are though, right?
Everything I've
done for your family
and this is my
severance?
I have kids.
You do?
Oh, you do. I knew that.
You are the most
familiar with it.
This isn't okay.
We voted, Griffin.
Democracy wins.
You get the gate,
we get the car.
Now, who'll take
the dead one out?
Can you
give me a hand?
Yeah. Oh, yeah.
You did what
you had to do. I get it.
You and me, we prioritize
the same thing, you know.
- Our careers.
- Families.
Uh, right. Well,
I mean, you know.
That's who the career
benefits. Yeah.
Sure. All I'm saying is...
we have to take care of our own
because if you plan on
them doing it for you...
All right.
Chop-chop, time to go.
- Good luck out there.
- Yeah, very helpful.
Thank you.
You should be okay
once they see the baby.
He's in the tunnel.
We'll drive
down and get you
as soon as the gates open, okay?
You're
gonna do great.
You do have the
greatest chance of success...
You are most familiar
with the gate.
All right. Let's go.
Which car do we take?
How am I
supposed to know?
You have the keys.
That one.
Oh, shit.
Oh, sweetheart,
I'll be back for you.
I promise you.
Hey, Ridley, come on.
Hey, we gotta go!
Wait, where's Shep?
Seriously?
Tell him to hurry.
Just wait. Shepard,
what the fuck?
Shep, we
are leaving now!
I'm coming, Mother.
Oh, shit.
On behalf of the humans,
we hope, uh, this
makes things cool.
Griff?
Ridley! What do I do?
I really
don't understand.
This is what they
wanted. It's...
Face it. There's no
negotiating with monsters.
Oh!
Where did they go?
Hey, coast is clear. Let's go.
Fuck this!
So much for
that fucking theory.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I thought I understood.
We're not gonna defeat them
in the marketplace of ideas,
which is why I did the work.
I figured out their weakness.
You're all very welcome.
Well, are you gonna
share it with us?
- Out with it.
- I revisited
my research and
a recurrent trope
in the medieval
discourse, as it were,
happens to be that unicorns,
historically speaking,
can only be trapped
by one thing,
and I think Ridley here
knows what that is,
a pure-hearted maiden.
Wait, I'm sorry.
What are you saying?
I, I don't know how you come up
with these ideas, Sheppy.
Research. That's
how I get my ideas, Mom.
And you were always
dismissing them.
This is about Dad's
legacy, this is about...
He's right.
He's right. It's my
fault. I misunderstood.
No, no, no, no. Oh, honey, no.
It's my fault. It's...
It's all my fault. It's...
I don't get
it. What do they want?
We're running out
of time, all right?
You need to listen to logic.
You need to listen to reason.
That is the only way we're
making out of this alive.
There is a recognizable,
- pancultural pattern across...
- Wait here.
...a variety of folkloric
hunt/capture narratives.
Are you
snorting that shit?
And if we're serious
about... Yes, yes, I am.
Serious about
surviving this thing,
then we have to be prepared
to use her as bait.
You understand?
But you were on the wagon.
I thought you were
doing so well.
- I am doing well!
- Shepard, Belinda.
Ah. Elliot, there you are.
Tell her to get ready
to make herself useful.
She might have to assume
a position or something.
Oh, no, sorry, she
doesn't work for you.
Not directly, no.
No, actually, you know what?
I'm afraid the time has come
for me to tender my resignation.
In our family's hour of need?
And you call
yourself an attorney?
Do your vows mean nothing?
Best of luck in...
...your, uh,
continued survival.
They're coming for us.
Okay. We're
getting out of here.
Are you vaping? Do you vape?
No.
Sheppie, please.
We underestimated it.
More than I ever could
have possibly imagined.
I feel it, in my mind,
sanctifying me.
No, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no.
Baby, we gotta
go. We gotta go.
I know what we have to do.
All right. No
matter what happens,
don't stop running till
you get to the car.
- We'll ram the gate.
- Okay.
- Okay?
- Yeah.
Let's not make this
- into a whole big thing.
- Hey, let go!
No, no, no. This is
for the greater good.
Get the fuck
off me! You fascist.
Shepples,
I don't know.
Shepard,
come on. Come on.
Whoa!
Kitchen door.
Kitchen door. Go.
No!
Stay there.
What?
Come on.
I-I don't
think it saw us.
No. I think...
Aw.
Man, Griff did find my bow.
Now, I feel bad.
Listen, if this
is the end, baby,
- I want...
- I need to think. Okay.
Maybe if I filed off
a little bit more
- of this horn.
- Wait.
Your dad's oxygen.
Can we blow it up with
this? Isn't that a thing?
Yes. Pressurized
oxygen is flammable
and if it combusts,
then it will explode.
- But that's...
- How do you know that?
You don't know that.
You don't get it, Mom.
This is inside my brain.
It's firing my shit up.
I'm a genius now, okay?
That will destroy
our golden goose.
We don't need to do that
because I want a goose farm.
So they'll come to her
and then... Open this.
And then we pen them in
and we force them to breed,
then they'll be ours.
What the shit is this shit?
Oh.
They're gonna kill us.
I don't understand why
they would do this to me.
I think I made a mistake.
What the fuck were you thinking?
I don't know. I...
I was afraid we'd get nothing.
How could you do that to us?
Because I promised her.
I sat in that hospital
room and I swore to her
that I would do whatever I
had to to take care of you,
to make sure that you
didn't want for anything.
And that's on me.
Every decision, every day.
But I failed you both.
And you don't seem
to need the things
I thought I was
giving you, so...
Actually, maybe they were
just for me after all.
Either way, I...
I'm sorry I'm the one
you're stuck with.
If we don't make it out of here,
my sweet darling boy,
just know, despite...
Shut the fuck up.
Do you hear that?
I think it's in the kitchen.
I think it might be leaving.
Mommy!
No!
Mom!
When I
touched the horn...
I think Mom was there.
I saw...
No!
- Go to the car. Get out.
- Dad, no. Please!
Please! You can't do this.
No.
I love you.
Dad!
Do it, Sheppie.
Please... forgive me.
Holy shit.
Don't move.
I didn't actually to take that
many lessons with this thing.
Come on.
Hmm.
I don't think you wanna do this.
You don't know that.
Face the front.
You don't know anything.
This is my destiny.
Stay right there. Don't move.
Yes, I fucking
knew it would work.
I'm the businessman now, Dad.
Okay.
Okay. You proved
everyone wrong.
Now can you please,
please just let me go?
Shut up. Shut up.
Please.
Dad?
That's it. The future's
ours now, Elliot.
50/50.
You earned this, eh?
Good job, partner.
I knew you had potential.
We'll finish tying
these things up,
get 'em locked away,
breeding can start
first thing Monday.
There's so much to do, but
they're ours now, Elliot.
We'll
own them forever.
Oh, my God!
What the fuck were you thinking?
I... I
don't know. Ahh.
I didn't
really plan it out.
We need to get you help.
It isn't good.
It looks bad.
I need to put pressure on it.
I... I
couldn't let him do it.
I need the horn.
I need the flesh.
I think it went
deep. Where's your phone?
I need the blood.
Oh, fuck.
We... We... We need
to get you help.
It's okay. It's okay.
It's not okay. You're...
You're bleeding out.
Hey, tell me,
tell me, please.
What did they show you?
I don't know. I... I...
I was standing in
the road with you
and I was swept up in
some kind of current.
It was like a river
and it was taking me somewhere.
And even though I didn't know
what I would find
when I got there,
I wasn't afraid,
because I had this sense,
I had this feeling in the dark
that they were showing
me where they came from,
but not just them, us too.
And I think it's where we've
always been heading back to.
Where a part of Mom
was already waiting.
In a place where we
don't have to worry
about what we didn't figure out
while we were here.
I don't know. I wasn't
there for very long.
I hope you're right.
Maybe...
I'll be there... waiting.
I don't...
What, what...
What?
They were
just this way.
Fuck.
Real bloodbath
up at the Leopold Ranch, Chief.
Bringin' survivors
in for statements.
But I got a feeling you're
not gonna believe them.
Well, then
that would make them suspects.
- Over.
- Roger that.
You two better
have a good lawyer.
I know this weekend didn't go
how you wanted it to and all,
but wherever they take
us, we're gonna be okay.
I know.
I saw it too.
What the heck?
Sorry. Sorry.